Rohat Alp

Address Yunus Emre Sok. No:27/5 Narlidere, Izmir,

Turkey, 35320

Phone 539 454 8329

E-mail alprohat7@gmail.com

Highly motivated Sales Assistant skilled at using the software that is mentioned below to create exceptional communications, presentations, and spreadsheets meeting diverse administrative needs with extensive customer service and sales experience. During education time, has attended to Work&Travel program in the US, 3 summers in a row. Goal-oriented, well aware of the needs of sustainability and digital transformation.

Work History

2019-12 - 2020-03

Sales Associate

Shinju Ready Clothes W.L.L., Doha, Qatar

- Closed over 2000 QR in sales each day, including preparing contracts and processing order forms.
- Streamlined operations and prioritized tasks, allowing every staff to increase revenue by 25%.
- Maintained customer satisfaction while handling textile product returns quickly and professionally.

2019-01 - 2019-03

Internship (Start-Up Project)

Yanmar Turkey Makine A.S., Izmir , Turkey

- Gathered data from market research surveys by using social media and transferred them to system.
- Data edited by using Microsoft Excel and made it ready for entry.
- Edited Microsoft Powerpoint slides to describe project to Japanese business partners.

2018-01 - 2018-03

Interpreter/Advisory

IZFAS (International Fair Organizations), Izmir, Turkey

- Provided cultural input to speakers to help parties who did not speak similar languages communicate with and understand one another.
- Provided oral translations and interpretations for groups of clients from India and USA during Marble Fair, successfully maintaining pace with native speakers to deliver real-time comprehension.
- Collaborated with other offices and territories to plan and facilitate needs of participants from different countries.

Education

2014-09 - 2019-06

Bachelor of Arts: Economics

Izmir University Of Economics - Izmir - Turkey

- Majored in Economics which was %100 English education and awarded as satisfactory in terms of GPA and grade for graduation thesis.
- Compulsory second foreign language was chosen as Spanish and the level is B1 proficiency.

Languages



Publications - Projects

Rohat Alp (May 2019). "The Exchange Rate Volatility and Tourism in Turkey" - Graduation Thesis

 Eviews (Emprical Study), Microsoft Office (Excel, Powerpoint, Word), Regression Analysis

Plum Scooters (February 2019) - Applied Entrepreneurship Project (Pitching)

• Detailed Market Size Estimation, Advertisement Options, Financial Analysis

Affiliations

- Chef Ryan McCaskey, (Michelin 2-Stars Awarded), Acadia House Provisions -Acadia House Chicago
- Assoc. Prof. Alper DUMAN, Izmir University of Economics
- Mustafa Kemal Erdogan Shoshi (Chairman Of The Board), Yanmar Turkey Makine A.S.